naughtydatingusa.com 2016-06-16

# Naughty Dating USA :: Naughty Dating USA Member Privacy Policy

_Last updated on March 15, 2016_

### Proprietor

The owners and operators of this website including any mobile website (the "Website") and the dating and networking service offered via the Website (the "Service") is Venntro Inc. also trading as White Label Dating; Venntro Inc. is a corporation organized under the laws of the State of Delaware whose registered office is 425 Boylston Street, 3rd Floor, Boston, MA 02116, USA (“we”, “us” and “our”). 

We respect the privacy of each user accessing the Website ("User", “you”, “your”) and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle and protect personally identifiable information received from Users, and what Users can do to help protect that information. 

### Submission and Processing of Information

When you subscribe or sign up to the Website and/or the Service, we may ask you for certain personally identifiable information. This personally identifiable information may include information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, email address, mailing address and telephone number ("Personal Information"). 

If a User elects to subscribe for the Service or access one of our other fee-based services, the Personal Information of that User may also include certain financial information such as debit or credit card information provided by that User. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial information on the Website, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine necessary to support and process your activities and transactions, as well as to your debit or credit card issuer for their purposes. These third parties may include the debit/credit card companies, data processing companies and banking institutions used to process and support your transaction or activity. 

In addition, the Website automatically collects anonymous information about Users. For example, the Website automatically gathers a User's Internet Protocol address, which Internet Service Provider the User utilizes, statistics about how Users navigate through and use the Website, and information gathered through the use of a device known as a "cookie". Cookies are small pieces of removable data that are stored by the web browser on your computer, mobile phone or other device that identifies your computer, mobile phone or other device when you visit the Website. We use cookies to improve the Website and the services available to you. 

For more information about the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them, please see our Cookie Policy. 

Personal Information collected on the Website may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which we or our affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or customers maintain facilities. You acknowledge and agree that Personal Information you provide to us may be transferred outside of the country in which you reside. Providing such information will constitute your consent to any such transfer. 

### User Postings

Except as otherwise expressly described in this Privacy Policy, this policy only addresses the use and disclosure of Personal Information and other information we collect from you. 

In the course of your use of the Website or Service, including when you create a profile on the Website, you may elect to post or otherwise disclose information about yourself and others, which may include Personal Information or other personally identifiable information. You may also elect to communicate with others or upload content such as photographs. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected or used by others. Such postings may also appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. 

Furthermore, although we restrict access to portions of the Website to members of the Service, since the Service is offered through and accessible through a number of other websites in addition to the Website, any information that you post to the Website for access by members of the Website may be searchable and available to users of the Service who access it via different websites from the Website. 

You may also receive unsolicited messages from other parties as a result of such disclosure. 

Such activities are beyond our control and this Privacy Policy. You should therefore exercise discretion and extreme caution when disclosing any Personal Information or other information when using the Website or the Service. 

### Third Party Websites

The Website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. It is the User's responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that they are acceptable prior to use. A link does not constitute an endorsement of the content, viewpoint or accuracy of such websites. 

### Marketing Communications

By subscribing to the Services you agree that we may use your information to contact you by electronic mail (e.g. by email and SMS) (“Marketing Communications”) about offers, events, competitions, items or related activities that you may find useful, as well as other similar products and services offered by us or any of our related entities from time to time. 

You may receive Marketing Communications from us or any of our trading names, for example Venntro Inc., both during the term of your membership (whether full or basic) and after termination of your membership (or deletion of your account) unless you unsubscribe from receiving such Marketing Communications as set out below. 

We do not sell, trade or rent Personal Information of Users to other companies and partners, but if you give us your express consent, we may share your Personal Information (other than credit card information) with affiliates of ours and with other carefully selected companies that we believe offer services and products that would potentially be of interest to you. In no event will the Company share any credit card information of any User. 

If you wish to receive Marketing Communications from selected third parties, or if you would like to receive Marketing Communications from us about our non-dating related products and services or other third party products and services, you can indicate your consent by ticking the relevant opt-in tick box during the registration process. 

#### How to unsubscribe from receiving Marketing Communications?

If you have consented to receive Marketing Communications, you may always revoke that consent at any time by changing your settings at the Website or exercising the "unsubscribe" option in any Marketing Communications you get from us or from our marketing partners. 

### Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information

Transmission of data and information via the Website is not a secure or encrypted transmission method for sending your Personal Information, unless otherwise indicated on the Website. Accordingly, your attention is drawn to the fact that any information and Personal Information carried over the Internet is not secure. Personal Information may be intercepted, lost, redirected, corrupted, changed and accessed by other people. 

Nevertheless, we are committed to using all reasonable efforts to protect Personal Information collected through the Website against unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Consequently, we limit employees' access to Personal Information collected through the Website to only those employees who need access to the information in the performance of their official duties. Employees who have access to this information are required to follow appropriate procedures in connection with any disclosures of Personal Information. 

The Company protects any debit or credit card information provided by the User by revealing only the last four digits of a User's debit/credit card number when confirming a subscription or order, but is required to transmit the entire debit/credit card number to its debit/credit card processor during processing. The Company will only store limited Credit Card or Debit Card information for the purpose of assisting with customer care enquiries. 

In addition, we set strict security standards to prevent any unauthorized access to your Personal Information once we have received it and wherever possible we will use adequate security software and working procedures to ensure the security of your personal data. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain accuracy, and ensure proper use of Personal Information, we have employed physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure the Personal Information we collect online. These measures include limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as electronic security systems and password protections which guard against unauthorized access. 

### Disclosure of Personal Information

We may disclose your Personal Information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries and our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries and affiliates. 

We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties if you have consented to such disclosure. In addition, we may disclose or provide access to your Personal Information to third parties without your consent: 

  * if we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your Personal Information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; 
  * if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case Personal Information held by it about our customers will, in most instances, be one of the transferred assets; 
  * if we ask a third party to carry out data analysis, cleansing and/or market research on our behalf; 
  * for the purpose of validating the identity of the user and/or conducting background checks; or 
  * if we have a good faith belief that we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation (such as in connection with a law enforcement request, judicial proceeding, court order or legal process), or in order to enforce or apply our cookie, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

### Changes to Personal Information

It is both in our interest and yours to store and process accurate Personal Information. If the Personal Information we hold about you is inaccurate in any way, where appropriate, you may have your Personal Information corrected by us on request. Please contact us to update any of your Personal Information by addressing the "Information Officer" via email at [dataprotection@venntro.com](mailto:dataprotection@venntro.com "Send an email to dataprotection@venntro.com"). 

### Children's Online Privacy

It is important to us that parents and guardians have control over what information is collected from their children online and how such information is or may be used. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA") imposes restrictions on commercial websites, including ours. It is our policy to be compliant with the requirements of COPPA and not to solicit or collect information about or from children age 13 and under. 

Beyond the requirements of COPPA, we require that individuals be age 18 or over to register as a member of the Service and thus it is our policy not to solicit or collect information about or from anyone under the age of 18. Users are cautioned, however, that absent a clear indication an online communication has been submitted by a person under age 18, the collection of Personal Information submitted to the Website will be treated as though it was submitted by an adult, and may, unless exempted from access by federal or state law, be subject to public access. 

In the event that we receive an online communication clearly indicating that it has been submitted by a person under the age of 18, under no circumstances will any Personal Information be published on the Website, be used for a purpose not intended by its sender or shared with third parties. 

If you would like more information about COPPA, please visit the Federal Trade Commission's official COPPA page at [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/). 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy and Transfers of Ownership

You agree that if we transfer ownership or management of the Website or our business and/or assets to a third party we may also transfer your Personal Information and any other data or information you have provided to us to such third party, provided such third party agrees to observe this Privacy Policy. 

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to accurately reflect how we gather and manage User information. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on the Website and, where appropriate and practicable, notify you by e-mail. All changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective upon posting to the Website. Please be sure to regularly check our Privacy Policy before using the Website. Continued use of the Website shall indicate your acceptance of any changes to this Privacy Policy 

### Disclaimer

The information provided in this Privacy Policy should not be construed as giving business, legal or other advice, or warranting as fail proof the integrity and security of information provided through this Website. While all reasonable attempts are made to provide accurate, current and reliable information, we recognize the possibility of human and/or mechanical error and the possibility that Users of the Site and other third parties may provide and/or publish information, graphics and images on the Site that are false, misleading, or inaccurate. Therefore, we make no representations as to the accuracy, completeness, currency or suitability of the information provided on this Website, and denies any expressed or implied warranty as to the same. For further disclaimers and limitations of liability regarding your use of the Website and Service, see our Terms of Use. 

### California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or affiliates for those third parties' or affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with whom it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request by email at  [dataprotection@venntro.com](mailto:dataprotection@venntro.com "Send an email to dataprotection@venntro.com"). Please note that it may take up to 60 days from receipt of your email to receive this notice. 

### Further Information

If you have any questions or comments about privacy or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [dataprotection@venntro.com](mailto:dataprotection@venntro.com "Send an email to dataprotection@venntro.com").
